Johnny Science Papers 1948-2000 (Bulk 1988-1998) MSS.268
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Projects
  - [St. Anthony: Religious Flyers, Pamphlets], various (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - [Stewart, Patrick - Clippings], various (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Straight to Hell: The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts - Number 54, c1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Strange Motorcycle Gangs: Cycle Outlaws - Special Issue Volume 1, Number 1, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "Swipe File" [Loose Clippings, Images], undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - "Teddy Bare" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - "Teddy Bear, Inc." [Letterhead, Notes], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - [Theater: Clippings], various (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - [Theater: Flyers], 1990s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - [Tom of Finland: Clippings], 1996 - 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - The Underground: An Erotic Emporium, Inc. [Catalog], undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - The Urban Herbalist - Number 11 [Zine], May 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Ursus Major - Volume 1 Number 1, Volume 1 [Newsletters], Winter 1996, May 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "The Valuable Intrinsic Worth of Individuality" by Johnny Science, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - VICE: Art + Entertainment Magazine - 1st Annual Photography Issue, September 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Wings Video Club - Catalog Number 6, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Series II: Correspondence
  - [Addressed to Dan Austen / Johnny Science], 1995 - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - [Addressed to Suzy Greengras], 1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - [Harley Davidson Notebook: Phone Messages], c1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - [Phone Sex File], 1995 - 1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - [Rachlin, Katherine "Kit"], 1988, 1994, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - [Schwartz, Bill], various (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - [Sohlberg, Eric Russell], various (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - [Sprinkle, Annie], c1996 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - [Subscriptions], various (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Series III: Photography
  - [Drag King Club Photography 1], undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - [Max's Kansas City Scrapbook Pages], 1970, 1978 - 1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - [Mixed Scrapbook Pages], undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - [Childhood & Young Adulthood - Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photographs], 1957 - 1980 (Box Binder 1)
  - [Drag King Club Photography 2], 1990 - 1995 (Box Binder 1)
  - "Linda / Les & Annie" Promotional Slides for Publication, 1989 (Box Binder 1)
  - [Mixed Personal Photography], c1998 - 1999 (Box Binder 1)
- Series IV: Objects
  - [Collection of Handmade Pins by Johnny Science], December 1982 (Box 6, Object ID: 268.2.0001)
  - [Collection of Buttons & Personal Items], undated (Box 6, Object ID: 268.2.0002)
  - "Grow a Pecker" Toy, undated (Box 6, Object ID: 268.2.0003)
  - Sony M-19V Microcassette-Corder, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 268.2.0008)
- Series V: Video recordings
  Conditions Governing Access
  Video materials have not been preserved and are currently unavailable to researchers.
  - "1st Live Show, Annie Special", January 12, 1999; cuid41457 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0001)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 62 minutes; Preservation Note: 5 hours of unrelated Manhattan Neighborhood Network footage not captured.
  - "Betty Dodson with Johnny", undated; ID: 268.0002 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0002)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    Original format: VHS
  - "Bob & Mo Show", undated; ID: 268.0003 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0003)
  - "Club Casanova '97", 1997; ID: 268.0004 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0004)
  - "Drag King Club - New Show", November 18, 1993; ID: 268.0005 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0005)
    Original format: Ampex 3/4" Tape
  - 1. "Drag King Show at Club Casanova, Meow Mix" 2. "Book Release Party for 'Female Masculinity' by Judith Halberstam", October 30 (no year); ID: 268.0006 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0006)
  - "Drag Kings 9BP", November 7, 1991; cuid41458 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0007)
    Duration: 114 minutes
  - "Drag Kings on Joan Rivers & Geraldo", 1992; ID: 268.0008 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0008)
  - "Drag King Club (That Show) - NY Times Rebuttal #2", November 17, 2001; ID: 268.0009 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0009)
  - "Drag Kings on Donohue", 1998; ID: 268.0010 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0010)
  - "Drag Kings at Maury Povich", October 20, 1999; ID: 268.0011 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0011)
  - "F/M Sampler from Lou Sullivan", 1984 - 1986; ID: 268.0012 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0012)
  - "He Was She Promo", 1989; cuid41459 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0013)
    Duration: 7 minutes; Preservation Note: Unrelated Dateline episode at the end of the tape wasn't captured.
  - "Geraldo I Master, Mistress Ecstasy's Erotic Circus", August 31, 1997; ID: 268.0014 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0014)
  - "Jerry Springer", July 16, 1999; ID: 268.0015 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0015)
  - "Johnny Science & Elvis La Femme", November 13, 1998; ID: 268.0016 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0016)
  - "JS Talking Head", June 1999, August 31, 1999; ID: 268.0017 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0017)
    Original format: Mini DV
  - "JS Talking Head at Kit's / Dred at Phoenix", undated; ID: 268.0018 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0018)
  - "Lauren Makeover Master Footage", January 12, 1998; ID: 268.0019 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0019)
  - "Linda / Les & Annie: A Female-to-Male Transexual Love Story", 1989; ID: 268.0020 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0020)
    Original format: DVD
  - "Linda / Les & Annie, Dred's Birthday", undated; ID: 268.0021 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0021)
  - "Maury Povich: Macho Men Who Are Really Women", June 28 1999; ID: 268.0022 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0022)
  - "Maury Povich DK Show #3", November 18, 1999; ID: 268.0023 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0023)
  - "Meow Mix Benefit with Dred, Justin Case", undated; ID: 268.0024 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0024)
  - "Mo in Express Studio (Mo Part I)", undated; ID: 268.0025 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0025)
  - "New/Old Meow Mix = Club Casanova", March 26, 1999; ID: 268.0026 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0026)
  - "Opening Night of Club Casanova - Michael Wakefield", March 31, 1996; ID: 268.0027 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0027)
  - "Ricki Lake: Lives of T/S, Gender Science Show", undated; ID: 268.0028 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0028)
  - "Simon: 8mm Tripod Camera Copy", undated; ID: 268.0029 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0029)
  - "Springer: Hermaphrodite Talk Soup Clip", undated; ID: 268.0030 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0030)
  - "Science / Max's / Von LMO / DK Misc - 1st Shoot at MNN", December 9, 1997; cuid41460 (Box 9, Hi8 ID: 268.0031)
    Duration: 64 minutes
  - "That Show with Johnny Science: Episode 1", 1998; cuid41461 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0032)
    Duration: 68 minutes
  - "That Show First Season Sampler", undated; cuid41462 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0033)
    Duration: 87 minutes
  - "That Show with Johnny Science #6", December 11(no year); ID: 268.0034 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0034)
  - "That Show with Johnny Science - Lauren Hastings", October 23 (no year); cuid41463 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0035)
    Duration: 165 minutes
  - "That Show with Johnny Science 18", March 5 (no year); ID: 268.0036 (Box 9, Media ID: 268.0036)
  - "That Show with Johnny Science: #1 - 2", 1998; cuid41464 (Box 9, Vhs ID: 268.0037)
    Duration: 82 minutes
- Series VI: Sound recordings
  Audio materials have not been preserved and are currently unavailable to researchers.
  - "Best of Both Worlds T = 67, Johnny Science", undated; ID: 268.0038 (Box Shared Fales 106, Quarter inch audio reel ID: 268.0038)
  - "Basement Rehearsal Blondes", undated; ID: 268.0039 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0039)
    Original format: Audio Cassette
  - "Boys & Girls Music Co.", July 1, 1984; ID: 268.0040 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0040)
  - "Bryan Ferry, Leonard & Suzy Singing", undated; ID: 268.0041 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0041)
    File Plan
  - Commercial Recordings, various (Box 11)
    This is a collection of 17 commercial and assorted recordings from Johnny Science's personal library.
  - "Francis the Great", July 24, 1975; ID: 268.0042 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0042)
  - "Fred Jorio - Sexstravaganza Tribal Sextrax", 1989; ID: 268.0043 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0043)
  - "1 )Fred's New Stuff; Fred Jorio: New Soul Songs; 2) "What a Man" S&P edit #2; "Montobi" Jorio (sextribe mix), September 1998; ID: 268.0091 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0091)
  - "Howard Stern Aircheck", May 27, 1988; ID: 268.0044 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0044)
  - "I Miss You Now", undated; ID: 268.0045 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0045)
  - "Joelle, Suzy & Jeff Singing & The Glen Echo Tapes", undated; ID: 268.0046 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0046)
  - Microcassettes, 1986 (Box 11)
    This is a collection of 22 microcassettes of assorted recordings from Johnny Science's personal library. They are housed in an annotated cigar box.
  - "New Beats One Through Six", June 1992; ID: 268.0047 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0047)
  - "Originals", undated; ID: 268.0048 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0048)
  - "Originals: Tape Given to Bryan Ferry", 1975; ID: 268.0090 (Box 14, Audiocassette ID: 268.0090)
    Duration: 29 minutes
  - "Refridgerator - Live at Max's", May 28 1980; ID: 268.0049 (Box 10, Audiocassette ID: 268.0049)
    Duration: 76 minutes
  - "The Rok Band Demo & Howard Stern", undated; ID: 268.0050 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0050)
  - "Suzy Greengras & The Rok Band in Concert at Chapter Arts Center, Wales", August 18, 1977; ID: 268.0051 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0051)
  - "Science - 13 Songs" [Empty Audio Cassette Case], 1977; ID: 268.0052 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0052)
  - "Science", undated; ID: 258.0053 (Box 10, Media ID: 258.0053)
  - "Science Demo Master", undated; ID: 268.0054 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0054)
  - "Science Demo (Mixed Down)", 1980; ID: 268.0055 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0055)
  - "Science: The Ancient History; The First Science Demo", 1979; ID: 268.0056 (Box 10, Audiocassette ID: 268.0056)
    Duration: 11 minutes
  - "Science: Final Mix I", 1980; ID: 268.0057 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0057)
  - "Science: Final Mix II", 1980; ID: 268.0058 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0058)
  - "Science at Max's", March 19, 1980; ID: 268.0059 (Box 10, Audiocassette ID: 268.0059)
    Duration: 54 minutes
  - "Science Live at Max's", undated; ID: 268.0060 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0060)
  - "Science Live at Max's (Black Label)", undated; ID: 268.0061 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0061)
  - "Science Live Demo", undated; ID: 268.0062 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0062)
  - "Science at Max's with Von LMO", undated; ID: 268.0063 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0063)
  - "Science Max's LP Remastered", undated; ID: 268.0064 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0064)
  - "Science - Live Demo", 1985; ID: 268.0084 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0084)
  - "Science LP - Ruff Mix", 1978; cuid41193 (Box 10, Audiocassette ID: 268.0065)
    Duration: 86 minutes
  - "Science LP - Ruff Mix", undated; ID: 268.0066 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0066)
  - "Science: Instrumental Final Mix", undated; ID: 268.0067 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0067)
  - "Science at Max's / Rehearsal at Scance's", undated; ID: 268.0068 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0068)
  - "Science Rehearsal - Wooster Street Studio", May 15, 1984; ID: 268.0069 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0069)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Legal Tender Studios", undated; ID: 268.0070 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0070)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Scance's with Joe Montag on Synth", undated; ID: 268.0071 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0071)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Robert's", October 30, 1983; ID: 268.0072 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0072)
  - "Science Rehearsal Including Darker Day Away", undated; ID: 268.0073 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0073)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Scance's with Joe Montage on Synth (1st Half)", undated; ID: 268.0074 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0074)
  - "Science Rehearsal at Moogtown", undated; ID: 268.0075 (Box 10, Media ID: 268.0075)
  - "Scramble It" by SE Greengras, 1980; ID: 268.0076 (Box 10, Audiocassette ID: 268.0076)
  - "Son of Science", undated; ID: 268.0077 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0077)
  - "Story of Dictation, Mike 1", undated; ID: 268.0078 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0078)
  - "Suzy & Lenny Lopate on Air Phone-In", undated; ID: 268.0079 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0079)
  - "Suzy Greengras Live at WBAI", 1974; ID: 268.0080 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0080)
  - "Suzy Greengras - Unstuck in Time", undated; ID: 268.0081 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0081)
  - "Suzy on Guitar - The Fat Lady of Limbourg", undated; ID: 268.0082 (Box 14, Audiocassette ID: 268.0082)
    Duration: 62 minutes
  - "Tim & Suzy Live", undated; ID: 268.0089 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0089)
  - "Von LMO at Max's", July 4, 1981; ID: 268.0083 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0083)
  - "Von LMO: Future Language LP", 1981; ID: 268.0085 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0085)
  - "Von LMO International Shortwave Pirate Broadcast", August 15, 1980; ID: 268.0086 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0086)
  - "Von LMO Rehearsal", July 14, 1992; ID: 268.0087 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0087)
  - "Winter Heart, Carey, New Androgyny Riff", undated; ID: 268.0088 (Box 14, Media ID: 268.0088)
- Series VII: Data Storage
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
  - "Vol I: Johnny Science", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0001)
    Format: Memorex IBM 2SHD
    Capacity: 1.44MB
  - "Vol II: Johnny Science", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0002)
  - "Drag King Club - Promo Stuff", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0003)
  - "IBM = AOL Chat Room 'BelAmi27,' Max's Letter", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0004)
    Format: Maxell MF 2HD
    Capacity: [unknown]
  - "Johnny", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0005)
  - "Johnny Science 3", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0006)
    Format: MAC100 Iomega
    Capacity: 100 MB
  - "Johnny Science Z2", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0007)
  - "That Show/Johnny Science CG Credits #1", undated (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0008)
  - [Mixed Personal Photography], 01/16/2007 (Box 11, Disk ID: 268.3.0009)
    Format: CD
- Series VIII: Comic Books, 1964-1997
  - Amazing Spiderman, The, May 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Amazing Spiderman, The, Dec. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Battlefield Action, Aug. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Boris Karloff Tales of Mystery, Jan. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Brave and the Bold Presents 3 Battle Stars, The, Feb./Mar. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Car 54, Where Are You?, Jan.-Mar. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dracual Lives, July 1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fightin': Air Force, Sept. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fightin': Navy, Oct. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Haunted Tank, The, Aug./Sept.1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - I... Vampire! Starring in the House of Mystery, Sept. 1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Man From U.N.C.L.E., The, Nov. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Mar. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Nov. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Sgt. Fury and his Howling Commandos, Jan. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Mar. 1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Mar. 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Oct. 1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Sept. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, Oct. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Sgt. Rock's Easy Co. in Our Army at War, July 1965 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Trinity Angels, Nov. 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - The Twilight Zone, Oct. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - War Heroes, Oct. 1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - War Stories Combat that Incredible Story of D-Day Invasion at Normandy, Oct. 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Projects
  - The Eulenspiegel Society: Pro-me-thee-us - A Sexual Minorities Report - Volume 1, Issue 1 [Newspaper], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Eulenspiegel Society: Pro-me-thee-us - A Sexual Minorities Report - Special Introductory Issue [Newspaper], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "The Eyes of Age" by Johnny Science, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club [Administrative File], c1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club Balls [Posters], [no year] (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club - Club Casanova [Posters], undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club - "Diane Torre's Drag Kings & Subjects" [Poster], February 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - F2M Fraternity: Drag King Club - "Life on Mars, An Alternative Cabaret" [Posters], [no year] (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "It's the Cut, Dr. Freud: Why One Woman Loves Men's Clothes" by Ingrid Sischy, 09/13/1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Jovian Gentlemen: 1997 Calendars (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - [Leather: Oversize Images], various (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - [LBGT: Events Posters], 1991 - 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "The Master Has a Big Bone For His Dog" [Illustration by Johnny Science], 08/16/1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - National Leather Association: 1995 Calendars, March - June 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - National Leather Association: "Fundamentals of Flagellation" [Posters], 04/29/1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - National Leather Association International: The Link - Living in Leather XI [Newsletter], July 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Oracle: Dwight Morrow High School - Volume 69, Number 3 [Newsletter], October 20, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - [Oversize Loose Images], undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Paper Tiger - Volume 2, Number 2 [Newsletter], November 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sage: United Community for the Aging [Newsletters], June - July 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Tom of Finland Boots Poster, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Tom of Finland "One Way" Poster, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Objects
  - "Priapus Incarnate" by Dan Austen [Illustration on Wood], June 1994 (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0004)
  - [Black Phallic Pillow], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0005)
  - Jovian Gentlemen Donation Tin, undated (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0006)
  - Jovian Gentlemen Umbrella, undated (Box 8, Object ID: 268.2.0007)
  - Leather jacket and cap, undated (Box 12)